Brandon Curtis



Brandcurtis43@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/brandcurtis



https://teras43.github.io/reactPortfolio/

Summary

I have multiple projects I have created using Angular 11, JavaScript, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Node.js, React.js, and Firebase among other things.

My Github: https://github.com/Teras43

I also have had 8 years of experience is customer service based upon multiple jobs that primarily require it.

In regards to computer hardware I have been building and using computers since I was young. I have built my own computer multiple times and I have knowledge on current computer hardware.

I also know 3D modeling based in Blender and have used it quite a bit.

Experience



3D Artist

Lucille Games

Nov 2017 - Apr 2018 (6 months)

Created 3D models for multiple games on the Roblox platform including weapons, armor, firearms, map assets, and skins for all the weapons, armor and firearms. I also assisted in polishing existing maps in the game, and creating new ones for multiple types of games. I used Roblox Studio, Blender and Adobe Photoshop.

Broadband Tech Support

ServerPlus

Jun 2015 - Nov 2015 (6 months)

In this role I would assist many customers per day as they called into us with issues regarding their DSL, Fixed Wireless or Broadband internet connections. I would go through and troubleshoot any issues with them and help resolve them in a timely manner.

Contact Collection

ROI Call Center Solutions

Apr 2014 - Jun 2014 (3 months)

Within this role I would call out to businesses in regards to their existing customer's want to switch to a Visa card for their payments.



Secondary ICS Supervisor

Walmart

Jun 2012 - Apr 2014 (1 year 11 months)

In this role I was the secondary manager for a team of employees who would be focused on unloading the freight trucks and getting the freight out to the sales floor so the next shift could stock it.

I also finalized the truck paperwork as we received it and assigned individual tasks to the team.

Education

Mountainland Technical College

Web Programming & Development, Computer Programming 2020 - 2021

Licenses & Certifications



AWS Academy Graduate - AWS Academy Cloud Foundations - Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Skills

Customer Service • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • Angular • React.js • MongoDB • PostgreSQL • Node.js • Firebase